Hello, it’s good to see you! We could use some help over here! 
Unfortunately, our owner, Paul Klee,misplaced his paint tins, so he can’t draw anymore! We want to find and collect them for him. 
But we can’t move without instructions! See those arrows over there? 
Drag and Drop them onto us, to make us move into that direction. Just know that we won’t stop moving until something blocks our path.
Let’s reach the paint tin together!


Oh, do you see that fish over there? It’s another one of Pauls creations. 
But now it blocks our path to the tin. Luckily, it responds to the arrows the same way we do. 
Drag and Drop one onto it to make it move away or use it to our advantage.

